(サクラ)ここじゃないわ！
This isn't the place.
Where are you?
《ナルト : どこだ…!?》
《サクラ : 私たち…➡
We've... finally made it this far!
ようやく ここまで来たのよ！》
Sasuke!
サスケ～!!
It seems...
(カブト)まだ…
見つけられないみたいだね。
they still haven't been able
to find him...
ここのアジトも 結構 広いからね。
This hideout is rather large,
after all.
苦労すると思うよ。
I think it'll be
a struggle for them.
詳しい地図でもあれば
話は 別だが…。
It'd be a different story
if they had a detailed map...
But unfortunately,
it's inside my head.
あいにくと それは ボクの頭の中だ。
(ヤマト)そう言えば ボクが➡
Did you think if you said that,
道案内しろ とでも
言うと思ったか？
I'd ask you to show me
the way?
…フッ。
ボクの任務は
ここで キミを見張ることだ。
My mission is to stand guard
over you here...
１人で キミを
本拠地に連れていくような➡
I've no intention of doing
something so risky...
as to take you inside your base.
リスクを 冒す気はない。
フッフッフッフ。
ソイツは 残念だ…。
That's too bad...
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
ここにも いない…。
He's not in here, either.
This is the last room
on this floor.
(サイ)ここのフロアは
この部屋で 終わりだ。
次のフロアへ 行こう。
Let's go to the next floor.
あぁ…！
Right...
ハァ ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
Naruto-kun...!
ナルト君！
二手に分かれて 捜してるんだ。
We're split up
into two search teams.
慌てず 少し 休んだほうが…。
You should stay calm
and rest a little...
Shut up...!
う… うるせえ…！
休んでなんか いられっか…！
I can't be resting!
もう少しで… サスケに…。
We're so close... to Sasuke...
《クッソ…。
Damn it...!
The damage I took when I morphed
into the Nine-Tails still hasn't...
九尾化したときのダメージが まだ…》
ハァ ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
ここにも いない！
He's not in here, either...
サクラ… 少し 焦りすぎだ。
Sakura...
You're getting too impatient...
ここは 大蛇丸の アジトの中…。
This is the inside
of Orochimaru's hideout...
It's possible that traps
have been set.
罠が張られている可能性も ある。
焦りすぎると
ヤツに 気づかれる恐れもある！
If we get too impatient,
he might find out that we're here.
I know that!
それは わかってます！
でも サスケ君が！
But! Sasuke-kun is...!
Sakura!
サクラ！
ナルトのほうは…？
まだだ。
What about Naruto...?
Not yet.
だが サスケを発見するのも
時間の問題だ。
But it's only a matter of time
before we find Sasuke...
慎重に行動しろ。
Act with caution!
はい。
I will...
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forgotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenain deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
EVERDAY hereafter is a shining day.
everyday kono saki mo shining day
Unchanging singin', a bright morning smile.
kawarazu singin' hikaru asa no smile
This is the last farewell on funny days.
kore de miosame no funny days
Leaping into the future I see. Go far, dream of my heart.
tobidatsu future mezashita go far kokoro no dream of
I'll go the distance, the endless sky is blue.
i'll go the distance mihatenu sora wa blue
I've hitched a ride on the star ship, this is the best forever trip.
norikonda star ship kore ga saigo no forever trip
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenai deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah, it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
Thank you my friend.
thank you my friend
Ah even now,
aa ano hi no koto
I still remember that day.
ima demo mada oboeteru kara
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah those days that will never come back.
aa mou nidoto sou modoranai days
Woah I'll go the distance!
woah i'll go the distance
The Picture Book's Story
It seems you're awake...
気がついたみたいだね？
Sai?
サイ…。
まったく キミは よく似ている。
Boy... you really resemble him.
My brother...
兄さんにだよ。
He was talkative and
he would lose his head...
口やかましく あわてんぼうで…➡
品がなくて… それに チン…。
He had no manners...
and his dick--
Well, never mind...
まぁ… それはいいや。
だけど そう…
キミのように 何をするにも➡
But yeah... like you,
he went all-out with
everything he did.
必死だった。
キミを見ていると…➡
When I look at you,
なんだか 兄さんのことを…。
I kind of remember him...
Sai?
サイ…？
Sai...! Hey, Sai!
サイ… サイってばよ。
What's the matter?
どうしたんだ？
I remembered...
I remembered...!
(サイ)思い出した…
思い出したんだ。
You mean...
それって…！
兄さんに見せたかった…➡
This is what I wanted
to show him.
２人の夢の絵を。
The picture of our dreams...
(大蛇丸)さて… サイ…。
Now then... Sai...
which side are you
going to take?
あなたは どちら側に
つくのかしら？
Striking Shadow Snake!
潜影蛇手！
Just as I thought. It seems
you're taking that side, huh...?
やはり そちら側のようね…。
サイとやら…。
Sai or whatever...
ここは オレが止めるってばよ。
I'll stop him here.
サイ… お前は サスケを捜してくれ！
Sai, you go find Sasuke.
Hurry!
早く！
わかった。
Okay... I'll find Sasuke-kun...
and save him!
サスケ君は ボクが見つけて助け出す。
So you came to take back
Sasuke-kun, huh...?
サスケ君を連れ戻しに
きたってわけね。
キミの執念はすごいけど
そう うまくいくかしらね？
Your persistence is impressive,
but will it really be that easy?
エロ仙人や 綱手のバアちゃんと同じ➡
It doesn't make any difference that
you're one of the Legendary Sannin
伝説の三忍だろうと 関係ねえ！
like the Pervy Sage and
Granny Tsunade!
お前を倒して サスケを連れ帰る！
I'll defeat you...
and take Sasuke back!
He's not here, either...
ここもいない…。
Naruto's Chakra...
ナルトのチャクラだ。
It appears something
has happened...
何かあったらしい… いくよ。
Let's go!
Right!
はい。
影分身の術！
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Striking Shadow Snake!
潜影蛇手！
Rasengan!
螺旋丸！
What happened to all
your energy from earlier?
さっきの勢いはどうしたの？
Your power...
The power of the Nine-Tails...
あなたの力は… 九尾の力は➡
There must be more to it
than this, right?
こんなものじゃないでしょ。
You're the one
who hurt Sakura, Naruto.
((サクラを傷つけたのは➡
キミだよ ナルト…。
You'll end up tormenting yourself
if you rely on the power...
これからも
この九尾の力に頼れば➡
of the Nine-Tails from here on.
自分自身を
苦しめることになるし➡
And it could turn into a power
that hurts your friends.
仲間を傷つけてしまう
力にも なりえる。
今回のようにね。
Like what happened this time.
If you want to save Sasuke,
do it with your own power.
サスケを助けたいなら
キミ自身の力で助け出せ。
If you want to see Sasuke...
サスケの姿を見たいなら➡
do it with your own eyes,
not the Nine-Tails'.
九尾の目ではなく 自分の目で…。
そして サクラを守りたいなら➡
And if you want
to protect Sakura...
(九尾の力ではなく 自分の力で))
do it with your own power,
not the Nine-Tails'!
フフ… 少しは本気を
見せてちょうだい。
Show me all you've got.
潜影蛇手！
Striking Shadow Snake!
Orochimaru again, huh...?
また大蛇丸か。
Naruto-kun is stalling Orochimaru...
《大蛇丸は ナルト君が
足止めしてくれている…》
And I'm sure the Captain
and Sakura-san...
《隊長とサクラさんも
ナルト君の援護に向かったはず》
have gone to back up Naruto...
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll!
忍法 超獣偽画。
Naruto-kun...
(大蛇丸)ナルト君… キミは
まだ生かしといてあげるわ！
I'll still let you live...
Please dispose of as many members
of the Akatsuki as you can, okay?
せいぜい 暁を １人でも多く
始末してちょうだいね！
Wh-What?!
なっ なに!?
More importantly,
I've got business with Sai...
それより私は
サイのほうに用があるから。
So I'll be leaving now.
(大蛇丸)これで失礼するわ。
はぁ…。
Where's Sai?
サイは？
サイは サスケを捜してるってばよ！
Sai's looking for Sasuke!
We have to do something
before Orochimaru finds him!
大蛇丸に見つかる前に
何とかしなきゃ！
I'll have to use up all of
my Chakra,
チャクラ 使い切っちまうけど➡
but I'll try searching with
my Multiple Shadow Clone...
多重影分身で捜してみる！
Captain Yamato and Sakura-chan,
you guys search that side.
ヤマト隊長とサクラちゃんは
そっち側を頼む！
What's this...?
(サクラ)これ…。
うん。
He... was able to remember...
アイツ 思い出せたんだ！
He said that's the picture of dreams
he wanted to show his brother.
それは 兄さんに見せたかった➡
２人の夢の絵なんだってさ！
They're both smiling...
２人とも笑ってる…。
Yeah... He smiled for real for
the first time when he drew that...
あぁ… その絵を描いたとき➡
初めてホントに笑ってた 心から…。
Smiled from the bottom of his heart.
ん？
Wh-What's this...?!
こ… これは…。
What's the matter?
(サクラ)どうしたんですか？
It was in Sai's bag...
(ヤマト)サイのバッグの中にあった…。
これは 暗部の者が
己のターゲットを記す暗殺リスト。
This is an assassination list
that has...
an Anbu Black Ops member's
own targets recorded...
いわば ビンゴブックだ。
It's called a Bingo Book.
An assassination list...?
暗殺リスト？
What are these "X" marks?
(サクラ)この×印… 何なんです？
これは おそらくターゲットを
すでに抹殺したという印だろう。
In all likelihood,
they're marks indicating targets
that have already been eliminated...
Why does Sai have such a thing...?
なんで そんなものを サイが…。
Look at this...
(ヤマト)見ろ！
こ… これって…。
Th-This is...!
なんで
サイの暗殺リストに… サスケの顔が!?
Why is Sasuke's face...
in Sai's assassination list...?
The clouds
drift accross
a distant sky,
The clouds
drift accross
a distant sky,
sora wa haruka
kumo wa nagarete
Far, far, far away,
beyond the horizon.
tooku tooku tooku
ni kogaretemo
Where will I go
from here and
what do I want?
Where will I go
from here and
what do I want?
doko o mezashite boku
wa fumidasu no ka
It's time to break
through my
fears and doubts.
It's time to break
through my
fears and doubts.
mayoi o ima
furikitte
Even though
I have a destiny
that I can't
escape from,
Even though
I have a destiny
that I can't
escape from,
nigeba no nai
unmei demo
I'm searching
for tomorrow.
asu o sagashite
Because the bonds
of friendship
keep me strong.
Because the bonds
of friendship
keep me strong.
boku o tsuyoku
suru no wa
nakama no kizuna
boku o tsuyoku
suru no wa
nakama no kizuna
Awaken the wild
side and let loose
the feelings!
Awaken the wild
side and let loose
the feelings!
mezamero yasei
afuredashita
kanjou
mezamero yasei
afuredashita
kanjou
Hidden within
my heart as I
smile recklessly.
Hidden within
my heart as I
smile recklessly.
mune ni himete
gamushara
no egao de
mune ni himete
gamushara
no egao de
And it's only when
I shout that the
truth is echoed.
And it's only when
I shout that the
truth is echoed.
sakebigoe wa
woah woah
shinjitsu dake
hibiku darou
sakebigoe wa
woah woah
shinjitsu dake
hibiku darou
My heart burns
and I'll hold on
to your hand.
My heart burns
and I'll hold on
to your hand.
kokoro moyase
soshite te o
tsunagou
kokoro moyase
soshite te o
tsunagou
If we're gonna
pursue those
eternal desires.
If we're gonna
pursue those
eternal desires.
yume ni
kometa eien
no negai o
yume ni
kometa eien
no negai o
Your prayer will
be granted,
motomeru nara
woah woah
Because the light
you seek lies there.
sagashiteru
hikari wa kitto
soko ni aru sa
sagashiteru
hikari wa kitto
soko ni aru sa
(ヤマト)今日のお題は
ボクも所属していた暗部についてだ。
Awaken the
beast within!
mezamero
yasei
(ヤマト)正式名称は…
Hmph,
It's you...
At last,
they meet again.
Finally.
Next Episode
Why is Sasuke's face
on Sai's assassination list...?
里じゅうから選りすぐりの
忍たちで構成される暗部は➡
正規部隊とは異なり➡
Then Sai's real mission was
to assassinate Sasuke-kun?!
火影直属の部隊として存在する。
It can't be...
He promised me that
he would save Sasuke!
(ヤマト)その特殊な任務の性質上
彼らの素性は極秘扱い。
I'm sorry to say this,
but it could all be an act.
常に 動物の面で顔を覆い➡
But...!
その情報は 何重ものセキュリティーで
守られている。
What was that noise?!
Can it be that Sai...!
No...!
Let's hurry!
Sai's location is not that far!
…はずなんだけどね。
ちなみに ボクが尊敬する
カカシ先輩も元暗部。
Reunion
Next time: "Reunion"
というわけで これが
その時代の貴重なフィルムだ！
NINJA ACADEMY
SPECIAL CLASS
"Anbu Black Ops"
The topic for today is the Anbu Black Ops
of which I once belonged.
まぁ 当時のことは
多くは語れないけど➡
先輩は 暗部時代も
すごい忍犬使いだったんだよ！
The formal name is the,
“Anbu Black Ops Special Tactical Unit.”
"Anbu Black Ops Special Tactical Unit"
Hokage
Advisor
Regular Unit
Medical Unit
The Anbu Black Ops is composed of shinobi
selected from within the village.
これ観せたこと 先輩には
絶対 内緒にしておいてくれよ！
Unlike regular units,
the Anbu Black Ops exists as a unit
under the direct command
of the Hokage.
Hokage
Advisor
Medical Unit
Anbu Tactical Unit
Due to the special nature
of the missions,
their identities are kept classified
and they always were animal masks.
And their information is protected
by a great deal of security.
At least, it's supposed to be...
By the way,
Kakashi whom I respect,
also used to be a member
of the Anbu Black Ops.
And now for a rare film from that period.
Well, most of the things that happened
back then can't be described.
But even back in
the Anbu Black Ops,
he was an amazing handler
of Ninja Hounds.
Please keep the fact that I showed this
to you guys a secret, no matter what.